

Ali Navidi Sari, Iran → +989339668289 2 years of experience ali_navidi24@yahoo.com

Portfolio: alinavidi.dev/

Frontend Developer

A 22-year-old frontend developer and a recent computer (software) engineering graduate, coding since 2018 and with over 2 years of experience in developing websites, trying my best to write clean code, higher up the performance and improve the user experience, always seeking to improve my abilities and learn new things.

Skills: Node.js Tailwind Next.js React.js JavaScript HTML) CSS TypeScript Cypress Express.js MongoDB SEO Git Bootstrap Svelte Remix

Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

- Improved tools to boost user interaction and deliver design versatility.
- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- $\hbox{-} Integrated enhancements into web design to improve user stickiness, smooth functionality, and boost load times. \\$
- Translated UX and business requirements into elegant code solutions.
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customer.

Oben Origin co.

Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

Projects

WESTERNAL | Frontend Developer - Backend Developer - Designer

Westernal is a social media based on songs. You can share posts that include part of a song, the whole song or music video with your followers and let the music talk for you!

 ${\sf JavaScript, CSS, Express, Cypress, Next. js, MongoDB, Node. js}$

CINEMA | Frontend Developer - Designer

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Cinema is a platform for watching and downloading movies. A user can login and buy subscriptions to watch the latest movies and series and learn more about cinema, actors/actresses and

TypeScript, CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

SARTEL | Frontend Developer - Designer

sari-sartel-westernal.vercel.app/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sartel is a website and PWA selling mobile phones and accessories.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

DASHBOARD | Frontend Developer - Designer

An admin dashboard website and PWA built with Next.js and Chart.js to manage website data and content.

 ${\sf JavaScript, CSS, Next.js, Chart.js}$

Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Languages

Farsi Native

English Advanced